<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Raising Awareness of Coding Design</title>
    <link>https://yohanboichut.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Raising Awareness of Coding Design</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 09:12:28 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yohanboichut.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GUI Testing without Service Implementations</title>
      <link>https://yohanboichut.github.io/en/posts/testfx-integration-test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 09:12:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yohanboichut.github.io/en/posts/testfx-integration-test-post/</guid>
      <description>This project illustrates a way to perform integration testing on GUI applications. The service layer is mocked using Easymock. Thus, we define use-cases in TestFx by mocking the service layer. Our test suite is organized in such a way that our future service implementation will inherit of the planned test defined initially with mocks. The whole source code can be found in Github.
The Service layer (model package) Our service is a very simple service whose goal is to handle a set of users (add a user, delete a user and get all users).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://yohanboichut.github.io/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yohanboichut.github.io/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Professor assistant at University of Orleans (France) Teaching  Web services (Rest and SOAP) Design patterns Test and Quality in Softwares Crypto systems and security JEE (JSP/servlets and Struts) JFx  Research fields  System verification Rewriting techniques and their approximations   This space is dedicated to the sharing of exercices, thoughts, experiments I have done with my students since 2008 in different fields of programming listed (but not exhaustively) above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://yohanboichut.github.io/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yohanboichut.github.io/en/contact/</guid>
      <description> Follow me @YBoichut Contact me at yohan.boichut@gmail.com.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>